Experience

YAZ MEDIA

Video Producer (Videography, VFX & Motion Graphics) 08/2024 - Present Dubai, United Arab Emirates Achievements/Tasks

> • Etihad Credit Insurance Content Production • Gitex 2024 Coverage Coursinity and Clickup Commercial

V-PATCH

Creative Producer (Video, Photo, Designing, Animation) 06/2023 - 08/2024 Dubai, United Arab Emirates Achievements/Tasks

> • Porsche Middle East Event Coverage. •Use of AI in Food Photography, Reel Creation VFX Reels

SOKEN

Video Producer / Graphic Designer 10/2022 - 05/2023 Dubai, United Arab Emirates Achievements/Tasks

• UI Design for Ministry of Interior KSA. Soken App Monthly Report Template. • App Promo Video for Soken

ARTKASH STUDIOS

Senior Digital Content Lead/Co-Founder 03/2022 - Present, Dubai, United Arab Emirates Achievements/Tasks

> • Branding for an Auto parts shop. • Podcast Production for Politix. • Product Photography for MIP.J Store. • Video Production For BeVIP Rental car & Munich Motor works Dubai,UAE

CXO GLOBAL FORUM

06/2021 - 03/2022, Islamabad, Pakistan Achievements/Tasks

• Successfully Managed all the Coverage of the CxO Global Digital Summit. • Production of CxO Rendezvous Show. • Production of CxO Weekly News Roundup.

KAHANI STUDIOS

Production and Designing Head 12/2019 - 05/2021, Islamabad, Pakistan Achievements/Tasks

• Window ad design for Dao Proptech. • Product Photography and E-commerce Designing for Sufas Shop on Amazon. • Brand Shoot for Malbus Pk. Product Shoot/Photography, • Digital Posts for Alpha Men Skincare Brand.

TGRS ISLAMABAD

VideoProducer & Graphic Designer 02/2019 - 11/2019, Islamabad, Pakistan Achievements/Tasks

 Promo for Master Mind with Umair Jaliwala. • Production of the Umair Jaliawala show. Social media Ads for Zumba Training Classes.

TECHVILLA COLLEGE OF INFORMATION TECHNNOLOGY

Graphic Designing Video Editing Tutor 06/2017 - 11/2019, Mardan, Pakistan

Education

NUML Islamabad

Bachelor in Mass-Communication 2017 to 2021 Islamabad Pakistan

Islamia College and University ntermediate (FA)

2015 - 2017 Peshawar Pakistan

Kashan

Multifaceted Visual Creator: Expert in Videography, Photography, Editing, VFX and Design

My Website:

https://kashanamjad.com

Address:

Dubai, United Arab Emirates

Phone:

+971 50 544 1914

Fmail:

kashanamjad1113@gmail.com

My Portfolio





https://www.instagram.com/that.filmy.guy/ https://www.behance.net/kashanamjad

About Me

With a comprehensive background spanning 7 years in videography, 5 years in photography, 6 years in video editing, 3 years in motion graphics, 6 years in graphic designing, 1 year in 3D animation, and 4 years in product photography, I bring to the table a versatile skill set to craft visually engaging content across diverse mediums. My extensive experience positions me as a seasoned professional adept at creating compelling visuals across a spectrum of creative disciplines.

Certifications

#GenGeo Storytelling for Impact: Video March 2022

Learned from world-class National Geographic photographers, videographers, and visual designers.

NUML Art Competition

Participated in NUML Art Competition as Poster Designer and secured 3rd Position.

See My Poster

NUML Art Competition

September 2018

Participated in NUML Art Competition as Poster Designer and secured 2nd Position.

2 times Winner

(AFAQ Science Model Contest)

I participated in the division mardan and District Swabi Science model Contests and got the first position in both contests.

Poster Exhibition

January 2018

Organized Poster Exhibition at NUML Islamabad Mass-Comm Department.

Kids Reader Design

October 2019

Designed a kid's Reader book. It consisted of Alphabets pages and different topics for kids' Growth.

#ItOnlyHappensInPakistan

July 2019

Participated In DW and Dawn.com Documentary Contest. the Documentary is based on a poor $\mbox{\it Man}$ who had a tea stall but didn't compromise on his daughter's education.

Watch Documentary

Graphic desgning NMUN

October 2020

Worked as an social media graphic designer for the 2020 NUML Model united nations islamabad.

Skills

VideoGraphy
Photography
Adobe Premiere Pro
Adobe Aftereffects
Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator
Final Cut Pro
Devinci Resolve
Adobe Indesign
Adobe Lightroom
Blender
Digital Marketing
Motion Graphics